All right, and Project 3 is This or That.
For this project, we wanted to solve
group dining indecision and waste times.
This or That simplifies
restaurant discovery into a fast,
single-device swipe interface
that finds a common consensus
among friends.
So here I have where I want to go,
any constraints, and who's eating.
It's going to build a deck for us
and allow Phil plus Alan to go through
and then find and combine interests
at the end.
All right, so this is for Phil's turn.
As you can see, it came up
with a few locations.
Phil is easygoing,
so he likes all the locations.
And then for Alan, we're just going to
go ahead and like maybe one
to show that it's matching correctly.
All right, and then after it goes through
everyone's turns,
it then aggregates the matches
and produces this final page,
which shows El Dorado Cafe
as a unanimous decision.
Down here, you can also see it highlights
the likes that Phil made,
as well as the ones that Alan made.
To guarantee bulletproof execution,
we prioritized a zero-friction,
pass-the-phone local setup.
Ideally, in future stages, we might have
this branch out to a multi-phone or,
you know, access from wherever you are
type of remote access,
so that friends can use this tool